César Cervantes

Jr Full Stack Web Developer

Summary

Jr Full stack web developer, specialized in the MERN stack. With experience developing freelance projects. Used to and able to work under pressure. Highly organized to work, with leadership, self-taught and fast learner. Like to keep my knowledge up to date and to increase my technical and soft skills.

Experience

Full Stack Web Developer | Freelance

October 2020 - Currently

- · Look for clients or projects, through online platforms or by generation a network of contacts.
- · Design web pages and web apps.
- · Analyze customer problems and propose solutions.
- ·Write code for the development of the websites.

Volunteer | Centro de Investigación en Computación (IPN)

March 2020 - October 2020

Develop a webpage useful for testing artificial intelligence's algorithms through a game of ultimate tic tac toe.

- · Develop the backend in Common Lisp; upload, store and execute the files with the algorithms for testing. Layout with a Common Lisp's library.
- · Develop the frontend; styles with CSS3, working of the game and consume the backend with JavaScript.
- **The original web page is in a private CIC's server, for private users. However, I made a copy with React and Node available at https://meta-gat.herokuapp.com

Degree Project | Unidad Profesional Interdisciplinaria de Ingeniería y Tecnologías **Avanzadas**

October 2017 — June 2018

Design and build a bio-inspired explorer robot

- · Study of the animal; get, manage and show the data.
- · Design mechanisms for the locomotion of the robot (walking and jumping).
- · Design of the control stage. (Programming and electronics).

Education

Bachelor of Science in Bionic Engineering | January 2015 – June 2020 (No degree)

Unidad Profesional Interdisciplinaria en Ingeniería y Tecnologías Avanzadas, Instituto Politécnico Nacional.

Details

Gustavo A. Madero, Mexico City, Mexico.

CP 07540

55 4914 8609

ces 29 1995@hotmail.com



github.com/CesarCervantes2908



in linkedin.com/in/cesar-cervantes-web

Technical Skills

- -Front-end:
 - React (1 year)
 - CSS3 (1 year)
 - HTML5 (1 year)
 - JavaScript (1 year)
 - Bootstrap 4 (less than a
- -Back-end:
 - Node Js (1 year)
 - Express (1 year)
 - MongoDB (year)
 - MySQL (less than a year)
- -Other programming languages:
 - Python (image processing, 1.5 years)
 - C (basic knowledge)

Languages

English

German